
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is a smart contract?",
    answer: "Programs stored on a blockchain that run when predetermined conditions are met",
    options: [
      "Online contract",
      "Programs stored on a blockchain that run when predetermined conditions are met",
      "Digital contract",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What powers the Ethereum Virtual Machine",
    answer: "Gas",
    options: [
      "Ether",
      "Bitcoin",
      "Gas",
      "Block Rewards"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Smart contract was first proposed by",
    answer: "Nick Szabo",
    options: [
      "Satoshi Nakamoto",
      "Elon Musk",
      "Nick Szabo",
      "Vatalik Buterin Gavin"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In which year smart contract was first introduced",
    answer: "1990",
    options: [
      "2001",
      "1990",
      "1994",
      "1996"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the name of the language used within Ethereum to implememt smart contracts?",
    answer: "Solidity",
    options: [
      "Solidity",
      "Kotlin",
      "C",
      "C#"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Smart contract is part of blockchain",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "False",
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Smart contracts have disadvantages like",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Dependency",
      "Non-Adjustable",
      "Implementation cost",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Smart contracts are of no use in case of supply chain use case of blockchain",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of these are smart contract platforms?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Ethereum",
      "Cardano",
      "Steller",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Advantages of Smart Contracts are",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Security",
      "Garaunteed Outcome",
      "Transparency",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },

];